Diet Agent a local-first desktop diet coaching agent.
This is the plan and personal information block
This here outlines the general direction of the plan.
You can set personal information and goals here.
You can make modifications here, ...
The LLM will reorganize the plan for you based on the information you provide.
Here is the new plan, the new daily goals
You can also set daily goals for yourself
This is where you set up API interfaces, language, notifications, and other settings.
Here is our menu, with many common dishes, more than 130 kinds.
You can also add your own, just describe it to the Agent.
This is our Agent chat window.
Next, I will briefly demonstrate how to plan a daily schedule.
The intermediate Agent will use tools and memory to solve problems based on the user's needs.
Here is our daily schedule.
And our weekly records
Of course, if you don't want to eat according to the plan, the Agent will notice the inconsistency and will remind you whether you want to make a change.
There are still many, many small features that have not been included due to time constraints.
Thanks!